Kheel Center Additional Cataloging Project Work notes /4107
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center Additional Cataloging Project Work notes
1877-1977
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Labor-Management Documentation Center (LMDC)
Kheel Center
/4107
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
7989264
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 16, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 30, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives.; Martin P. Catherwood Library.; Martin P. Catherwood Library. Labor-Management Documentation Center.
7989264
- 5010, 5272 International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 5011 Morton Singer, Papers, 1945-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 5012 Saul Wallen, Arbitration Awards (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 5012 Saul Wallen (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 5012 Saul Wallen cont. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 5012 Saul Wallen etc. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 5012 Wallen description (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 5012 Wallen (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 5012 Notes on the Saul Wallen Papers (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 5012 Saul Wallen - C Companies (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 5012 Wallen (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 5012 Saul Wallen - A Companies (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 5012 Saul Wallen - DEF Companies (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 5012 Saul Wallen - B Companies (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 5012 Saul Wallen - G Companies (Box 1, Folder 15)
- 5012 The Role of Personal Values in Arbitration. A Case Study of Saul Wallen (Box 1, Folder 16)
- 5013 Erie Lackawanna Railway Company Misc. Documents, 1903-1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- 5017 Frances Perkins to Frances White. Letters (Box 1, Folder 18)
- UMW Election Material (Box 1, Folder 19)
- 5025 Mabel Leslie (Arbitration Awards) (Box 1, Folder 20)
- 5032 Jacob Seidenburg. Injunction Study Data, 1935-1950 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- 5032 Jacob Seidenberg Injunction Study, 1936-1950 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- 5034 SUNA (Box 1, Folder 23)
- 5035m Letters to a Civil Engineer in N.Y.S. (Box 1, Folder 24)
- 5049 Trans World Airlines (Box 1, Folder 25)
- 5049 TWA and Flight Engineers International Association, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- 5084 Hawaiian Airlines Limited and Airline Pilots Association. International (Box 1, Folder 27)
- 5108 Amalgamated Clothing Workers, Rochester Joint Board (Box 1, Folder 28)
- 5109 NY Women's Garment Industry and the ILGWU Arbitration Records (Box 1, Folder 29)
- 5109 New York Women's Garment Industry (Box 1, Folder 30)
- 5127 Hays, Paul Arbitration (Box 1, Folder 31)
- 5130 Capital Airlines, Inc. w/ Int. Assoc. of Machinists Dist. 144 Arbitration Proceedings (Box 1, Folder 32)
- 5131 Sidney Holff (Box 1, Folder 33)
- 5140 PERB (Box 1, Folder 34)
- 5140 PERB (Box 1, Folder 35)
- 5141 Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Records description (Box 1, Folder 36)
- 5141 Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Records drafts and notes (Box 1, Folder 37)
- 5141 Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Records (Box 1, Folder 38)
- 5141 Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Records, 1919-1932 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- 5143 Anna Weinstock Schneider Papers (Box 1, Folder 40)
- 5143 Anna Weinstock Schneider Papers, 1921-1969 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- 5245 Black letters (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Labor Play Scripts, 1915-1943 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- 5276 IWO (Box 1, Folder 44)
- 5276 IWO (Box 1, Folder 45)
- 5279 American Federation of Teachers (Box 1, Folder 46)
- 5293 NSTA Description (Box 1, Folder 47)
- 5293 NYSTA Original - Description (Box 1, Folder 48)
- 5293 NYSTA Notes (Box 1, Folder 49)
- 5295 Illinois Central and Gulf Railroad (Box 1, Folder 50)
- 5298 NWLB Notes (Box 1, Folder 51)
- 5307 Consumer League of New York Records (Box 1, Folder 52)
- 5307 Consumer League NYS Notes (Box 1, Folder 53)
- 5314 NWLB (Box 1, Folder 54)
- 5470 Abraham Feingold Papers (Box 1, Folder 55)
- 5475 Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen. General Chairmen. Boston and Maine Railroad Records description (Box 1, Folder 56)
- 5475 Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen. General Chairmen. Boston and Maine Railroad Records (Box 1, Folder 57)
- 5138tr(1144) Miners for Democracy (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 5168mf SLP Sect A-F (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 5170 William Thaw letter, 1877 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  July 23, 1877
- 5170m William Thaw Letter, 1877 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 5171 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 5206 Local 1199 Descriptions Final (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 5206 1199 Drug Division (Box 2, Folder 7)
- 5206 Local 1199 Descriptions (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 5206 1199 Administration P/S (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 5206 Local 1199 Guild (Box 2, Folder 10)
- 5206 Hospital Div. 1199 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 5211 Labor Leaders - Biographies (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 5225 ALES (Box 2, Folder 13)
- 5225 ALES Descriptions - Typed (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 5389 US Anthracite Coal Commission (Box 2, Folder 15)
- 5391 NIRA (Box 2, Folder 16)
- 5435 NLRB/ OH (Box 2, Folder 17)
- 5465 Communist Party NYS Dec. (Box 2, Folder 18)
- 5489 Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad Company Agreements, 1914-1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- 5517 M.E. Brooks and A. S. Coater Collectors. Railroad Wage Reduction Movement Documents, 1931-1937 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- 5524 American Industrial Union (Box 2, Folder 21)
- 5525 Samuel Wolchek Correspondence and Minutes, 1935-1956 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- 5507 Ellsworth D. Opie Autobiography "Transition - An Autobiographic of Life", 1965-1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  1965-1966, 1974
- 5522 Edward Wight Bakke Papers (Box 2, Folder 24)
- 5522 E. Wight Bakke Papers (Box 2, Folder 25)
- 5522 description (Box 2, Folder 26)
- 5530 Ordway Tead Papers (Box 2, Folder 27)
- 5541 Philip Taft Collection (Box 2, Folder 28)
- 5562/5541 Philip Taft Papers (Box 2, Folder 29)
- 5574 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- 5597 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- 5001 AALL correspondence sub-series (Box 2, Folder 32)
- 5001 American Legislation for Labor Legislation Records general notes (Box 2, Folder 33)
- 5001 AALL Research materials sub-series (Box 2, Folder 34)
- 5001 AALL Organizational materials (Box 2, Folder 35)
- 5001 AALL Pamphlet collection publications (Box 2, Folder 36)
- 5001 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- 5001 American Association for Labor Legislation Records (Box 2, Folder 38)
- 5001 Draft description for the records of the American Association for Labor Legislation (Box 2, Folder 39)
- 5623 Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Legislative Board of New York Selected Files, 1910-1975 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- 5623 Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Legislative Board of New York Selected Files, 1910-1975 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- 5618 Wrege (Box 2, Folder 42)
- 5616 Rubinow Description (Box 2, Folder 43)
- 5616 Issac M. Rubinow (Box 2, Folder 44)
- 5616 Rubinow notes/drafts (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Jacob Seidenberg Arbitration Case Files, 1935-1977 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- 5478 RED Notes (Box 2, Folder 47)
- 5478 RED Notes (Box 2, Folder 48)
- 5478 Railway Employees' Department AFL-CIO Records (Box 2, Folder 49)
- 5478 RED AFL-CIO Description Draft (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Originals (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Project Summary Sheet (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Originals for Data Gathering Sheets (Box 3, Folder 3)
- History Notes (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Categories (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Field Definition Table (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 5225 ALES Xerox Material (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Manuscript Cataloger (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Accession (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Misc. (Box 3, Folder 10)
- I.A., 1917-1920 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Los Angeles, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- 5618 Charles D Wrege Research Materials on History of Management (Box 3, Folder 13)
- 5168 Socialist Labor Party of America Records, 1877-1907 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Transcript and Thank you Letter (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Resume and Letters (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Misc. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Reports to Refile (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Misc. (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Places to Call (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Cards (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Academy of Management (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Resume etc. (Box 3, Folder 23)
- 5538 James Hill Papers (Box 3, Folder 24)
- 5581/5103/5103a Slips (Box 3, Folder 25)
- 5581 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- 5581/5103/5103a NY ST Bd Medication Notes (Box 3, Folder 27)
- 5103/5103a/5581 NYS Bd of Medication Description - Notes on Processing (Box 3, Folder 28)
- 5602/5120/5133 Gabriel N. Alexander Arbitration Case Files/Records (Box 3, Folder 29)
- 5602/5120/5133 Gabriel Alexander Arbitration (Box 3, Folder 30)